elitelikes.com 2015-08-18

# Privacy Policy - EliteLikes

Home / About

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which EliteLikes collects, uses, maintains, and discloses information collected from users of this Web site (each, a “User”).

**Privacy**   
User’s privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

**How We Collect Information**   
Users will never be implicitly added to any marketing lists. Users subscribe to mailing lists by clicking on a checkbox in a form that clearly states what the checkbox means. The User has the right to opt-in or opt-out at any time.

**The Information We Collect**   
EliteLikes may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. EliteLikes may also collect information about how Users use our Web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Web site or the domains from which Users originate. We may use “cookies” to track how Users use our Web site. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the Users’ PC and use to identify the User should they visit the Web site again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our Web site.

**How We Use Information**   
EliteLikes may use personally identifiable information collected through our Web site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by EliteLikes and otherwise to enhance Users’ experience with EliteLikes. EliteLikes may also use information collected through our Web site for research regarding the effectiveness of the Web site and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of EliteLikes.

**How do we protect your Information**   
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financial’s, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Disclosure of Information**   
EliteLikes will not disclose information collected from Users to third parties. However, we may disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from Users to investors and potential partners. Finally, we may transfer information collected from Users in connection with a sale of EliteLikes’s business.

**Maintenance of Information**   
Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures.

**Affiliated Websites**   
We may offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to EliteLikes in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.

**Security Alerts**   
EliteLikes reserves the right to contact you about security issues concerning your website. You may opt-out from receiving security alerts, but it strongly recommended that you treat them with the highest importance.

**Your Consent**   
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**   
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Our Guarantee To You**

Its simple. Our guarantee to you is that you will get the Facebook likes you paid for or your money back. We do our very best to serve our clients to the fullest extent possible. We are your partner to make your Facebook promotions the best they can possibly be

**Questions**   
If you have any other questions or concerns regarding any part of this privacy policy, please do not hesitate to **contact us** through this website.
